<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Buhr Construction</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</description>
    <link>//</link>
    <atom:link href="//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Good hardworking and friendly people...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“Thank you for the excellent job your men did on my roof. You have real good hardworking and friendly people working for you. Thanks again.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Dores&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//testimonials/2014/05/29/good-hardworking-people/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//testimonials/2014/05/29/good-hardworking-people/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Great job and crew really worked hard...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“My husband and I would like to thank you for taking care of our roof so fast—especially after all the rain we just had. Your crew did a great job and they really worked hard. You came highly recommended to us, and we will surely recommend you to others. Thanks again!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Paula and Mike&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//testimonials/2014/05/26/great-job/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//testimonials/2014/05/26/great-job/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Treated us fairly and honestly throught the project...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“We felt that all your employees did a great job in keeping the good reputation you have established. Tom was always good at answering our questions and keeping his appointments with us. He was friendly, made good suggestions and always returned our phone calls. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also felt lucky that Junior was the foreman for this project. He is a skilled worker who helped us to make decisions that improved the final look of our house. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The remainder of the workers, Brian, Scott and others who helped, were also very hard workers. We appreciate their friendliness and good manners. They seemed to enjoy their work while doing it in a professional way. We would also like to thank you. We felt you treated us fairly and honestly throughout the project. Again, thanks for a great job!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Kevin and Carol&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//testimonials/2014/05/24/treated-us-fairly/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//testimonials/2014/05/24/treated-us-fairly/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The thought of having work done on the house no longer feels like an ordeal...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“We want to thank you for a wonderful job. It was a joy working with Buhr Construction. Your men were fantastic. They did a perfect job and left the yard spick and span. In the past weeks I have recommended Buhr Construction to four of my friends who needed roof work. The thought of having work done on the house no longer feels like an ordeal. I look forward to working with you again.”&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//testimonials/2014/05/23/wonderful-job/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//testimonials/2014/05/23/wonderful-job/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Your crew was super and we are thrilled...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“Just wanted to let you know how very pleased we are with your work. Your crew was super and we are thrilled with our new roof. We will most definitely spread the good word.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Darrell and Lori&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//testimonials/2014/05/22/very-pleased/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//testimonials/2014/05/22/very-pleased/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Professional, timely and easy to work with...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“We want to compliment you on your project coordinator Tom, and the crew that worked on our house. Tom was professional, timely and easy to work with. The crew that was sent to our house to install the roof and skylights were so hardworking and did an excellent job. Please pass on to all of them that we are very pleased. We highly recommend Buhr Construction.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Mary and Dave&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//testimonials/2014/05/20/best-experience/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//testimonials/2014/05/20/best-experience/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hats off to you and your man...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“I want to compliment you and your crew for the exceptional job you did replacing the roof on our home. Corey and his crew were the most polite and professional group of young men I have had the pleasure of being around in a long time. I realize having the owners hang around can get a little taxing at times but they always answered my questions and explained things to us. Again, hats off to you and your men for an excellent job on our home.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Mark and Mary&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//testimonials/2014/05/15/exceptional-job/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//testimonials/2014/05/15/exceptional-job/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I surely will recommend Buhr...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“I’m very satisfied with the roof and skylights you installed at my cottage. I was especially pleased with how clean you left the cottage, both inside and outside. I surely will recommend Buhr Construction if the occasion occurs. Once again, thanks for a job well done.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Dan&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//testimonials/2014/05/13/will-recommend-buhr/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//testimonials/2014/05/13/will-recommend-buhr/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nice to work with...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“Your crews were sure nice to work with during the projects at our house. Thanks for a nice job. The new roof looks great!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Dave&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//testimonials/2014/05/13/nice-to-work-with/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//testimonials/2014/05/13/nice-to-work-with/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Many thanks for the great new roof...</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“Many thanks for the great new roof at our place in Marshall’s Point … and also for leaving such a clean and neat area after the job.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Linda&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>//testimonials/2014/05/07/great-new-roof/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">//testimonials/2014/05/07/great-new-roof/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
